Dubofsky, Melvyn Papers 6218
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Melvyn Dubofsky Papers
1970-2010
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Dubofsky, Melvyn
6218
27.72 cubic feet
27.7 linear ft.
Papers.
8258686
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, September 10, 2013
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, March 04, 2016
Biographical / Historical
Melvyn Dubofsky is the Bartle Distinguished Professor of History and Sociology at the State University of New York at Binghamton.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 6218 AV: Melvyn Dubofsky Audio-Visual Materials
Dubofsky, Melvyn, 1934-
8258686
- Miscellaneous correspondence (Box 1)
  - A Schofield and N Asher (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Amer. Labor History (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Author's Guild (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Alex Blair (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - P. Blatz, Tenure Pros. Etc. (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Ed Boyle - Labor Guild Materials (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - D. Brady (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - S. Buroud (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - J.W. Cobert - Proposal on butte Redirection (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Canada Council Evals. (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - R. Carwardine Corres. (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - D. Christopher's, diss. (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - colwill, B. (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - B. Crawford, Diss. Presp. (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - J. Cumbler, Louisville U. Evaluation (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Dalhousie UC Heron PhD Defense (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Colin Daws and K daws (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Ileen DeVault Tenure File (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - V Di Santo (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Eastern Forum Workers Assn. (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Dana Frank: Tenure Eval. (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - S. Fraser Corres. (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - P. Fruedlander, Grant Application (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Encycl of US Labor Conflict (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Paul Garner Corres. (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - German Amer. Studies Conference and F.V. Berlin Lecture 2-78 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - German Encyclopedia of Local and Economic History (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - H. Gitetman: Proposal and Rec. (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Glenn, Susan (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Jim Green U.S. worker in 20 C (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Rexie N. guard Corres. (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Dane Gurowsky - PhD (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - H.J. Harris - Corres. Papers (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - J. Higginson Neurology Research Proposal (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Toshio Hisada (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Taylor Hollander (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - T. Houlihan Dir, etc. (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - D. Harrell Hayward Bus (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Intl. Comm. On Monuments Bucharest, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Sanford Jacoby (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - R Jeffreys - Jones Corres (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - JAH Editorial Evaluations (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - G juretic Corres. (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - M. Kazim (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - S. Kelman diss. Fund Eval (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - V. Kelmer corres. (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - H Kumeldorf (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - C. Klemegger (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - S. Klimkiw Grant Proposal (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - G. Korman Book Revs. (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Paul Krauss - Stems (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Jennifer Langdon (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - G. Lerinque (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - W. Licht Mss. - 19th C. RR Workers, Princeton U Press (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - N Lichtenstein corresp. (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Dare Lists Maxwell Sci. PhD (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Marine Workers Historic Assn. (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - D. McBride, Misc. (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - Paul McBride Papers (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - Joe McCartin (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - Larry McDonald, Corres. (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - R. McElraine Thesis (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - R. McGuire Recs. (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - Corres: W. H. Mammaring (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - Jim Mulherim - UC Berkeley (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - Marcy May, Corres. + PhD (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - SUNY - B Lab - Microforms Guide (Box 1, Folder 67)
  - Jennifer Miller (Box 1, Folder 68)
  - Mitrano, troy (Box 1, Folder 69)
  - NLRB - OH Transcripts NYSSI + LR (Box 1, Folder 70)
  - M and S Nash Diss. (Box 1, Folder 71)
- Miscellaneous correspondence (Box 2)
  - U Nebraska Press - Appeal to Reason (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - NEH Evaluations (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Melvyn Dubofsky -NEH Summer Stipend Proposal, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Dan Nelson Rubber Workers (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - NYS Labor History Assn. V.P. and Health File, 1978-1980 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - T. Nomma, Corres. (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - R. Oestreicher: Projects (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - OUP-JLL Book (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - B Palmer - Diss. (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Platke, David (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - C Post - Diss. (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Random House Folder Documents (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Renshaw, Patrick R.G. (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Promotion + Tenure Evals, Misc. (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - M Robin, Canada Council Research Proposal Eval. (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - M. rogers Res Files (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Sage Local Sci. history Laws Bd. Of Eds - S Engerman (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - N Salvatore (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - R Schatz File (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - rick Schmidt: Diss. R Borardi (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - L. G. seretan, Canada Council - Social (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Alan Singer, UMW 1920s (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Patrizia Sione (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Cronin "Worker's Control Essays" (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Judith Stein (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - C. Stephenson SUC Bankruptcy Tenure (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Carol Stevenson: Prospectus + Recs. (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Paul Street (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Rich Street - General materials (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - R Street Niss. On Calif. Forum Workers (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - P Taft LH Prize Comm (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Tenure, Promotion Evals, etc. (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - External Tenure Eval + Dan Leab (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - T Thomas (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - EPT Corres. (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Chris Tomlins (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - L Trefousse (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - TV History Course: Labor in Industrial Era Dollar CC (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Tyler - ILG Bills: Labor + Politics (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Van Time - Diss. (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Vaudagna, M. (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - S. Vittoz Materials (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Asher - Walkowitz Tenure (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Sam White (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Winslow File (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - P. Warthman: Corres. (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - G. Zahavi Diss. (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Mark Zaltman (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Gregor, Bob (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - E. Zivich Diss. (Box 2, Folder 50)
- Miscellaneous correspondence (Box 3)
  - Guggenheim Fellowships Application (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - NDEA Institute (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - NEH Fellowship Application Lewis Project (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - NEH Summer Seminar's NTP's (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - NYT Microfilm: Business and Industry Journals (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - NEH Summer Seminar, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - NEH Summer Seminar (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - NEH Seminar Proposal, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - R. Keeran Tenure (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - A. Kradtor, Reduced Persuasion LSU Press (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - J. Laslett Soc. Mss. U Cal Press (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Laslett - Lisset: WSBA Tyler (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - N Lichtenstein Mss. "CIO in WW II" - Cambridge U Press (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - U Mass Press Book (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - S. Mazzoda Mss., Chi. Bands (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - "AFL and Politics 1870-1925" Princeton U Press (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - U of N Carolina Press: Political Extremism Mss. (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - M McColloch, "White Cellar Workers, 1940-1970" Temple U Press (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - J.J. Schacht, Tele Workers Unions Mss., U of I Press (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Renshaw, Derfler, and Green Miss. (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Stephenson - Asher SUNY Press LH Essays (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - UWM Job (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - WSU - LH Position (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - U of Washington Job (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Applications - Warwick (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - NYS ILR Job (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - U of Mass. Job (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - U of Ill. Chicago - Job (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - U of Florida Job (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - U Tenn - Chair (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - UW - Job CUNY (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - IUP: Vera Buch Weisland Miss. Autobiography (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - M. Wyman Miss.: Hard-Buch U of Cal Press Reports (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - HBJ - Weisberger Book on American worker, 1870-1970 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - D. Thelen (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - NYC Salon Mss. (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Social and Economic Statistics Darfiume (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - NYT - Salon Readings (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - State + Social History Applications (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Fellowship Applications ACLS (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - ACLS Applications (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Amer. Philo. Society Applications (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Eval: G Carey, The Paterson Rutgers U Press (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - TY Crowell: Labor in the Industrial Age (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - L Derfler - Mss. On Socialism (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Truman Era Book Critique (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - U of Ill. Press - Ill. LH Mss. (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - G. Eggert Mss. (Maverick Steel - Master) - Bucknell U Press (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - SIU Press - Fetherburg - Mother Jones Mss. (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - Carl Gerswig Mss. Eval (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - SUNY - Press, Jas. Gruss NLRB, 1937-1947 V. 2 (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - Holt, Rinehart: Poverty and Powerlessness (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - JJ Huthmacher: Proposal Labor Essay (Box 3, Folder 53)
  - B. Johnpoll American Secularism Mss. Cornell U Press (Box 3, Folder 54)
  - Indiana U Press, MFD (Box 3, Folder 55)
  - Jennifer Zecher (Box 3, Folder 56)
  - Professor Dubofsky - Recommendations Jen Zecher (Box 3, Folder 57)
  - Grad Student: Courses and Files (Box 3, Folder 58)
  - Referree Letters (Students) (Box 3, Folder 59)
  - Princeton Ill Press, JLL Paper (Box 3, Folder 60)
  - Fellow Recommendations - Arum, Nielson, etc. (Box 3, Folder 61)
  - NEH - Paula - Urban Economics Proposed (Box 3, Folder 62)
  - NEH: JJ Clare (Box 3, Folder 63)
  - D Walkowitz, NEH Proposed for TV Program on Troy, NY (Box 3, Folder 64)
  - I Yellowitz R of L Proposed (Box 3, Folder 65)
  - American quarterly - Essay (Box 3, Folder 66)
  - U of Texas Press - Byrkit Mss. Life and Labor in Arizona (Box 3, Folder 67)
  - J Cape: WSBA (Box 3, Folder 68)
  - Cornell ILR - Mss. Eval.: ACLU and Wagner Act (Box 3, Folder 69)
  - D Brundage (Box 3, Folder 70)
- Various seminar papers (Box 4)
  - NEH Summer Seminar 1980 Proposal (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - AHM - Labor History Text (FR Dulles) (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - SUNY Binghamton (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - SUNY Binghamton Dubofsky Files (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Research Proposals (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - To: World Labor Group (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - WLG, 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - US - Soviet World Labor Confs., 1983 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Trans National Social movements (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - FBC Worker Movements, 1980-1981 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - FBC: Workers' Project, 1979-1980 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- John Lewis research files (Box 5)
  - Employee Attitudes, 1931-1938 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - JSS and UMW in 1920s (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Lewis + Germer - Loyalty to UMW and AFL, 1933-1934 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - CIO and AFL Unity Negotiations, 1937-1942 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - CIO States as of, 1939 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - CIO Executive Board Minutes, 1939 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Lewis and 1940 election (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - JLL and S Hillman (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Coal Industry, 1923-1946 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - JLL and 1939 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Labor's Non-Partisan League and 1936 Election (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - SWOC (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - UAW (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Lewis, J Wayne State University (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Notes on Lewis, UMW and Eval Industry (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - JLL Speeches Written by WJ Lauck (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Early Years (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Lewis's Ideology (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - CIO Beginnings (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Lewis - FDR and New Deal, 1933-1939 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - JLL Mss. - Quadrangle Fund Legal Pensions, etc. (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - John L Lewis State His of Wise holdings (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Misc. Notes on JLL and Banks + Etc. on Coal (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - D Brady and Readers of ILL MSS. (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Penn State Labor Archives UMW - CIO Papers (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Xerox Orders on JLL (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - NA Materials - Lewis and UMW (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - JL Lewis (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - FDR Library Materials and Notes (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - FDR Library - Lewis Xerox Materials (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - S. Rogers on Biography (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - JLL Misc. File (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - JLL Early Years UMWJ (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Thomas H Lewis (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - George W Lewis (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Alexander Howat (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - John Hunter Walker (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - John P White (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - John Brophy (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - William A Mitch (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Thomas Kennedy (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Powers Hapgood (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - William Green (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Adolf F Germer (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Frank Farrington (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Van Amberg Bittner (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - Al Hamilton (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - Frank J Hayes (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - UMWJ 1917 (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - UMWJ 1918 (Box 5, Folder 50)
  - Lewis Challenge Gompers for AFL (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - 1918 Lewis Attempt to Unseat James Maurer Because of Stand on War (Box 5, Folder 52)
  - UMWJ 1919 (Box 5, Folder 53)
  - UMWJ 1920 (Box 5, Folder 54)
  - UMWJ 1921 (Box 5, Folder 55)
  - UMWJ 1922 (Box 5, Folder 56)
  - UMWJ 1923 (Box 5, Folder 57)
  - UMWJ 1929 (Box 5, Folder 58)
  - UMWJ 1925 (Box 5, Folder 59)
  - UMWJ 1926 (Box 5, Folder 60)
  - UMWJ 1927 (Box 5, Folder 61)
  - UMWJ 1928 (Box 5, Folder 62)
  - UMWJ 1929 (Box 5, Folder 63)
  - UMWJ 1930 (Box 5, Folder 64)
  - UMWJ 1931 (Box 5, Folder 65)
  - UMWJ 1932 (Box 5, Folder 66)
  - 1933 Lewis Blacklist Against Brophy and Hapgood Hapgood to James Maurer, Socialist Party Coll. Duke (Box 5, Folder 67)
  - UMWJ 1933 (Box 5, Folder 68)
  - UMWJ 1939 (Box 5, Folder 69)
  - UMWJ 1935 (Box 5, Folder 70)
  - UMWJ 1936 (Box 5, Folder 71)
  - UMWJ 1937 (Box 5, Folder 72)
  - UMWJ 1938 (Box 5, Folder 73)
  - UMWJ 1939 (Box 5, Folder 74)
  - UMWJ 1940 (Box 5, Folder 75)
  - W Jett Lauch Diaries 1936-1941 (Box 5, Folder 76)
  - Panama Ill Years (Box 5, Folder 77)
  - JLL Early AFL Career (Box 5, Folder 78)
  - 1919 Coal Strike (Box 5, Folder 79)
  - Mine Strike 1919 (Box 5, Folder 80)
  - JLL and Jacksonville Agreement (Box 5, Folder 81)
  - UMW Correction Proceedings, etc. 1911 (Box 5, Folder 82)
  - Carlione: Interviews for JLL Project (Box 5, Folder 83)
  - Lewis and AFL Presidency 1921 (Box 5, Folder 84)
  - MUMW Journal (Box 5, Folder 85)
  - JLL and Harrison Family (Box 5, Folder 86)
  - Howat and Kansas Affair (Box 5, Folder 87)
  - Progressive Miners of America 1923 (Box 5, Folder 88)
  - Farrington, Frank (Box 5, Folder 89)
- John Lewis research files (Box 6)
  - NRA and JLL and Early New Deal (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - JLL, Homer, and Natl.1929-1932 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Conference of Progressive Miners 1927 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - 1922 Strike (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Brophy and Save the Union Campaign (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - State of OMWIA, 1933-1934, by EA Wieck (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - West Va. Coal 1920s (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Rise to Power (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Panama Case up thru JH (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Newspaper Info 1920s - JLL (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - JLL Character + Personality (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Illinois District 12 Struggle and Reorganized UMW 1928-1932 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - JLL and Natl 1920-1929 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - JLL, Mexican and LA Salon 1936 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - JLL, FDR, and Origins of WW II (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Foreign Affairs (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - William Walter Miller MA MWJ and the War (Box 6, Folder 17)
- Miscellaneous conference papers (Box 7)
  - Cornell ILR Talk, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    Scope and Contents
    feb 7
  - Binghamton U Papers (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Labor Course Sept - Oct 2000 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - AHA: Boston 2001 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - PA History Assn. Keynote, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    Oct 20
  - SSHA 1999 Meeting Fort Worth (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Dubofsky, Melvin SUNY - Binghamton (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - NALHC - Oct 1998 Panel on MD (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - PCB (AHA) Panel on Teamsters (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - NYLHA Meeting, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    May 9
  - OAH Indianapolis Labor and Rose Papers April 4, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Stockholm Conference: Int'l, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    March 13-14
  - Lattimer Massacre, 100th Anniversary, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    Sept 12-13
  - Jimmy Carter Conference Feb, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Carter Conference, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    Feb 20-22
  - NALH Conf - WSU, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    Oct
  - Oct 1995: NLRA - NLRB Conf. Wash. D.C. (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - School of Industrial and Labor Relations (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - D Brumberg (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Terre Hante ISU - Dila (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - ISU Melvin Dubofsky (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - SSHA - annual Meeting, Baltimore Nov, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Paterson, NJ Conf. 200th Anniversary (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - IU Dubofsky (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - U of Wash Seattle - Bridges Grad. Summer, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - PCB (AHA) Conf. - Aug 1992 Paper State and Labor (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - NYLHA Keynote Address, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 27)
    May 19
  - State and Labor Paper (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - PSWLH Keynote Address April, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - 1990 AHA Program Proposal (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - York college Lecture, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 31)
    March 21
  - UMW Conf., 1990 (Box 7, Folder 32)
    Oct 6
  - Penn state conference Center (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - PSU - UMW 100th Anniversary Conf., 1990 (Box 7, Folder 34)
    Oct 18-20
  - AIW from FDR to Reagan Conf., 1989 (Box 7, Folder 35)
    May
  - Conf: WW I and Workers G., 1989 (Box 7, Folder 36)
    Sept. 22
  - Professor Mark Perlman (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - AHA: Littleton - Grunwold Prize Committee (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Book Ads and Reviews (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - Amerika Haus Library Prof Dubofsky (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - Queens College History (Box 7, Folder 41)
- Miscellaneous chronological correspondence and odd files (Box 8)
  - Misc. Correspondence (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Current Correspondence, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence. Misc., 1978 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence. General, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 1959-1960 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 1961-1963 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 1964-1966 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, 1966 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - General Correspondence, 1969-1970 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Current Correspondence - General, 1970-1972 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Per. Correspondence. Misc., 1977-1978 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - SUNY Faculty Exchange Scholar (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - E Resslark: JLL For TV (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - NEH Fellowship Panel Aug, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - America history - Culture (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Fulbright Distinguished (Box 8, Folder 17)
- Miscellaneous conference papers (Box 9)
  - PNWLH Conf., 1986 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    May 17
  - Southern Labor History Conf. ATL, GA, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - MD IWW and Culture of Poverty (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - OAH 1968 IWW Paper (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - AHA Paper, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Paper: Fordham in US GEMDEV Paris conf. (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Paper: Technology and US Union (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - SSRC: LA Labor History Conf., 1983 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - W. German lecture (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Conference AIW + Political Parties, FDR to RR (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Clermont - Ferrand Paper on Union Violence (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - U of Venice and Florence Talk Corres. Workers in Colonial America (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Paper: FBC, History and Soc. Scenes (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - U of Sussex Talk Corres (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - ILR Labor history conf. Ithaca, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 15)
    April 21-23
  - Misc.: Armstrong Papers (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Harvard business School Seminar, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 17)
    April 11
  - Paper, Rise and Fall of Revolutionary Syndicalism in the United States (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - OAH - Reno (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - OAH Meeting S Gompers Session, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 20)
    April
  - Smithsonian Labor conf., 1986 (Box 9, Folder 21)
    Nov 14-16
  - Penn State U Murray - SWOC USA Conf, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 22)
    Nov 13-14
  - Lowell Industrial history Conf., 1986 (Box 9, Folder 23)
    Oct 31 - Nov 11
  - Toronto NALH and amer. Legal History Confs., 1986 (Box 9, Folder 24)
    Oct 24
  - OAH - NYC April 10-13, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - AHA Paper, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 26)
    Dec
  - IUP (PA): Soli and Frag, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 27)
    Oct 23
  - WSU: NALHC (CIO), 1985 (Box 9, Folder 28)
    Oct 24-26
  - Lec. A People's Republic: Amor. Workers Politics (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Papers: For SSRC Conf. on Workers in LR Work Spanish Translator (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Sidney Hallman Talk (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Lectures on Social and Comparative history (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - J L Lewis Lecture Indiana, PA (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - NIU-NEH LH Conf. (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - NIU "Future of american History: toward a Synthesis" (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - Tech and America Labor Paper (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - Wright State U Dayton OH Tech. Labor Conf. (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - Upstate NY Grad History Forum: Cortland, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 38)
    Sept 23
  - SUNY - B women's history Conf., 1983 (Box 9, Folder 39)
    April 22-23
  - OAH - 1983: Ch and Comm. (Box 9, Folder 40)
  - M Uriefsky - VCU New Deal, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 41)
    Mar
  - Yale Law School - Workers' Control conf., 1983 (Box 9, Folder 42)
    Feb. 17-18
  - Ethnicity + Labor in Contracts Conf. PA, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 43)
    Oct 1
  - ILR Student Seminar on 1930s, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 44)
    Oct 26
- Miscellaneous conference papers (Box 10)
  - Conf. on NYS History Buffalo, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    June 4-5
  - SUNY-Buffalo Solidarity Symposium, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    April 17
  - Johnson State LH Conf., 1981 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    Dec 10
  - Ithaca College, E. Mayrock Lecture Series, Fall, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - 3rd W.S.U. - N. America LF Conf. (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - SW Labor Studies Conf. UNM, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    Jan 1
  - Amer. Sre. For Legal History: Labor Law Panel, Oct, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - SSHA Conference - Rock, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    Nov 6-9
  - NMSU Lecture: Hidden Heritage Labor and Reduction in S.W. (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - WSU Labor Conf. Oct, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - U Iowa - H Hoover: US History Conf. - JLL - April, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Past, Present, + Future of Amer. Labor Movement (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - SUC: Potsdam Lecture - US Ind. City + Labor Movement (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - NIU Lecture, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    Nov 15-16
  - ASU - SW Labor History Conf., 1977 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    March 4-5
  - OAH Session: Pana-IWW, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Fredonia LH Conference (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - AIHA - Baltimore - Nov 14-15, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - SUNY - B - Women's History Conference: Papers and Comments (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Salvatore LaGumina Papers + Comments (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Western history Conference - Workers - Yale, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Mann-Hayward Paper (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Zanne - Madison Corporate Labor Conference, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - IWW - NYC Talk, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 23)
    Jan 15
  - SUNY - Buf, Tolstoy College Lecture, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 24)
    Nov 1